### Rachel Lally

# 406-640-2928 | rlally89@gmail.com | https://github.com/rachlally

### **Summary**

A recent graduate of University of Washington's Coding Bootcamp looking forward to applying full-stack web development skills. 10+ years of experience in hospitality and construction management. I am focused, detail-oriented, and a problem-solver. Strong communication and collaboration skills.

# **Experience**

Sept 2022-Dec 2022,

Student, University of Washington

Succeeded in full-time, immersive program learning skills for modern web development. Front end and back end technologies covered. Created extensive portfolio that can be viewed at GitHub link provided.

Sept 2019-Aug 2022

## **Tasting Room Manager**, Stave and Stone Wine Estates

Managed two tasting rooms. Oversaw a staff of 25+ employees. Maintained high-end customer service in tastings rooms and event spaces. Responsible for maintaining POS systems. Conducted regular inspection of facilities to ensure best food and service standards are met.

Oversaw opening of new Wine Garden Space generating additional \$6,000 in weekly revenue (within two months matching half of gross weekly revenue). Grew Event Offerings to generate additional revenue.

July 2012-May 2019

### Manager of Guest Services, Cascade Ridge

Managed all accounts payable and receivable. Developed task lists to ensure daily, weekly, and monthly goals were met. Oversaw housekeeping and maintenance staff. Point of contact for all homeowners, renters, contractors, and vendors.

## **Operations Supervisor**, Cascade Ridge

Managed cleaning and maintenance of 10 private residences and community Lodge. Oversaw inventor for lodge, homes, and property. Assisted in training Lodge Attendants and Maintenance Staff.

### **Education**

Full-Stack Web Development, Coding Bootcamp University of Washington, December 2022 Bachelor of Arts in History & English University of Puget Sound, May 2012

# Skills

JavaScript
MySQL
Mongo
Communication
HTML
CSS
RESTful APIs